The Magical Revolution
of the Reincarnated Princess and the Genius Young Lady
Who is it?
I came over to play!
Again?
You're gonna get in trouble.
It'll be fine!
C'mon, let's do some experiments!
Are you sure it'll be all right this time?
O-Of course! My theory's perfect!
Is it really?
Yes, it is!
You said that last time,
and then there was a huge explosion.
Even I got in trouble with Father.
We'll be okay this time!
It'll work for sure!
No. I'm not hanging out with you anymore.
You don't even feel bad about what happened.
Okay, I get it!
What happened last time
was my fault! I'm sorry!
So...
Let's shake hands and make up!
Well, I guess I can play along
with you for a little bit.
Yeah! Thanks!
Let's go, Al!
I still remember how warm her hand felt.
Which is why...
I still can't forget how cold it felt
when our hands separated, either.
Water Cutter!
Water Lance!
Icicle Prison!
Water Hammer!
Al!
You're not afraid at all.
You need to stop taking me so lightly!
The super-regeneration of a vampire...
That's gonna be trouble.
Water Bullet!
Ice?
I know your Mana Blade is weak
against physical attacks.
And you think that gives you
a strategy against me?
If you do, you didn't think
this through very well.
Well, let's just find out...
if that's true or not.
Icicle Rain!
I fear for our future.
How ironic it is.
No matter how strong you
demonstrate yourself to be,
you will only be feared by the people.
You'll be called a heretic,
and no one will recognize your worth.
Which one of us is the heretic?
I know better than anyone
that I'm a heretic.
You know it yourself, and yet
you make no effort to change?
What was it you hoped to accomplish, then?
What did you hope to become?
Answer me!
Answer me, Anisphia Wynn Palettia!
I'm just me. I can't become anyone else.
I just had a love for magic, that's all.
Even after all this, you're still
hiding behind stupid word games?!
You'll just pretend to accept it,
while you keep lying to yourself
and deceiving those around you?!
You aren't fit for this kingdom.
I know that.
But even if I can't use magic,
I know it's still a sacred thing.
I still have faith.
I believe in magic, and I love it.
I always will!
And that's more than enough
to make me happy.
Even knowing the thing you
love will always betray you,
you'd still say that?
You truly are arrogant.
I will surpass you. I have to.
I can't move forward if I don't!
Anisphia!
Eu...phylli...
Please, don't speak!
I... know...
I should... give up...
There's nothing... I can do...
except scream... the way I did...
Scream?
Lady Euphyllia...
If I had blood... magic...
You need blood?! I'll...
No.
Stay as you are, Lady Euphyllia.
I will—
Pardon me.
No... The pain won't go away...
How is Prince Algard able to move?
It hurts! It hurts!
Even after regenerating,
you still feel pain?
Lady Euphyllia...
Do you not wish to put a stop to this?
I...
Miss Anis!
I broke it!
I smashed the damn thing!
Is this the best you can do, Sister?
Stop fooling around! Look at me!
Am I not even worth existing
in your field of vision?!
I get it.
You're saying I should
fight to kill, aren't you?
Aerial Attack: Dragon Heart!
You're such...
a stupid little brother!
Not yet...
I'm... I'm not...
This is...
the end!
Why...
are you looking at me like that?
Euphie?
What good does it do for you two
to try to kill each other?!
You're both idiots!
You don't want to fight if it means
having to make that face, do you?!
You didn't want to kill him, did you?!
Yet you kept fighting...
hurting each other...
Are you a complete fool?!
Al...
It was nice weather.
The skies were clear, so I was looking up.
There's only one person I know
who'd be up in the sky like that.
Do you remember, Sister?
The day we escaped the castle.
Yeah.
Then we were attacked by a monster.
You stayed behind so I
could escape, and I ran.
I hid so it wouldn't find me.
I just trembled in fear
and didn't even breathe.
And you were the one who found me then, too.
You were always leading me by the hand.
You taught me so many things.
I really think
I was still human right up until that day...
Until the day you pushed me away.
It's true. I pushed Al away.
After that monster attacked us,
a rumor started going around.
A rumor that I had tried
to kill Al out of jealousy.
That's why I renounced
my right to the throne.
I wanted to prove that I had no interest
in inheriting the throne,
and no ill intent toward Al.
Sorry about everything.
You can be the next king now.
So don't worry!
That was the day...
our relationship changed.
Hey, Sister...
Why did you throw away
your right to the throne?
Why must someone who's
so much smarter than me,
who can show concern for others,
be scorned as unworthy of the throne?
I...
I know.
But still, you should be queen.
At least, I felt that way sometimes.
But the people who run this
kingdom will never let you.
A country that denies someone's superiority
and only adheres to old traditions
may have a glorious past,
but it'll never have a future.
So...
What choice is there
but to destroy it and start over?
Al...
It'll never be within my reach.
The true genius, the one who
truly cares for the people,
the one capable of earning
the proper qualifications...
is you.
Not me.
I shouldn't even have been born.
Because of me, you had to get hurt...
And if it meant you had to be hurt,
if it meant you'd have to feel this way...
I never should have been born...
Sister...
It hurts being unable to become
what you truly want to be.
Algard, why did you do such a thing?
I have nothing to say,
except that I was a fool.
Then I have no choice but to disinherit you.
Do you resent me?
No. If I harbor any resentment,
it's for this entire world.
I hated everything, from the moment
I was born up until this day.
Everything, you say?
That's quite the declaration.
No commutations or apologies are
needed with regard to my punishment.
I will comply with your orders.
You will hereby be exiled
to the borderlands.
Until your body is reduced to dust,
it will be put to use in service
of this kingdom. Understood?
I offer my deepest gratitude for
Your Majesty's great kindness.
"Your Majesty," eh?
I've failed as a mother.
I know I had a part in
nurturing your resentment.
I'm sorry, Algard.
My sin is my own.
Please, do not worry yourself over me.
I'm sorry I wasn't a better son.
Prince Algard,
could you tell us about the others
involved in this incident?
Of course.
Then, if you would follow me...
Sister...
Do you... remember this?
"Shake hands and make up," right?
I'm sorry.
If I had just lived a normal
life in this world,
you wouldn't have suffered so much...
Sister...
Thank you. And I'm sorry.
I'm so sorry I couldn't protect you.
After Prince Algard's
punishment was decided,
all the plans writhing behind the
cancellation of his engagement to me,
Euphyllia Magenta, came to light.
It all started when Master Moritz,
after learning who Lainie was,
discovered some research
materials about vampires.
As punishment for using her vampire powers
and Prince Algard himself in a plot
to obtain even greater authority,
the Chartreuse conspirators
were granted death
for threatening the king's authority.
Those who worked with them
were also severely punished,
leaving the castle in chaos.
We were not unscathed, either.
Both Miss Anis and Ilia are bedridden.
Only Lainie and I remain healthy.
And then...
the day of Prince Algard's departure
for the borderlands arrived.
I'm sorry to appear without notice.
Might I speak with Prince
Algard for a moment?
Er, but...
Um...
Prince Algard...
Lainie...
This was the only choice I had.
Feel free to curse me all you like.
You did do a terrible thing to me.
But it's all right.
I believe the Prince Algard
who was kind to me is real, too.
Real?
I know you only did all that
so you could use me.
But I felt happy...
So I don't think that kindness was a lie!
But it still hurt very much, and I
suffered a lot, so I won't forgive you.
I'll despise you forever.
Yes. I'll always remember, too...
To be both apologetic and grateful to you.
Euphyllia, I need to apologize to you, too.
I know you probably don't believe that...
No, that's not...
It's fine. Don't put up a front.
Though I suppose, for you,
that just came naturally.
You're the duke's genius daughter, after all.
But you can't be someone's
fiancée like that.
It's despicable. Not lovable at all.
How very rude you are.
Prince Algard...
Please forgive this one act of indiscretion.
I've already been disinherited.
Do whatever you want to me.
That really stings.
In truth, I considered
using my fist instead,
but I couldn't, of course.
That's for the best.
There's no one who'd say you're
like a little doll anymore.
No... If I could have faced
the problem properly,
perhaps I would have found another way.
I do apologize for falling short.
That said, you were absolutely
deplorable as a fiancé.
I'm impressed we both kept up that
horrible engagement for so long.
It's time.
I had hoped to apologize to Ilia
in person, as well, but...
I'll pass that along to her.
Also...
I know I'm really in no position
to ask this of you, but...
Take care of my sister.
A reaction to the seal on your back, is it?
I only helped you because
you said it was safe.
Miss Anis?
Al... I'm sorry...
Miss Anis...
Have pleasant dreams.
I'll be here beside you.
Episode Nine
The Sister and Brother, and for
Whom the Crown Is Intended
Episode Ten
The Royal Succession of Resignation and Fury